{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/4048","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4048","name":"Huntington Place-Wayne Hall Kitchen","address":"1 Washington Blvd","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Volume Services DBACenterplate","licenseNumber":"081581","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"-83.04924,42.32658","geojson":{"id":"4048","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.049237066,42.326580122]},"properties":{"name":"Huntington Place-Wayne Hall Kitchen","owner":"Volume Services DBACenterplate","address":"1 Washington Blvd","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"081581","establishmentid":"4048","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4211","name":"Huntington Place- Portables","address":"1 Washington Blvd","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3495","name":"Simon's Pizza","address":"1 Washington Blvd.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4140","name":"Cobo Hall-Eatsville USA/Solid Gold","address":"1 Washington Blvd","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3175","name":"The VU Restaurant and Lounge","address":"1 Washington Blvd","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3245","name":"Cobo Hall- Main Kitchen","address":"1 Washington Blvd.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1486","name":"Pizza Queen","address":"1 Washington Blvd.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4049","name":"TCF Centerl-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","address":"1 Washington Blvd","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3949","name":"Presto/ Andiamo Detroit Riverfront","address":"1 Washington Blvd","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1498","name":"Baskin-Robbins 31 Flavors","address":"1 Washington Blvd.","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4384","name":"Cobo Hall- Custom Dogs","address":"1 Washington Blvd","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"61736","inspectionDate":"2023-02-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not marked with a consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Cooking equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"57483","inspectionDate":"2022-03-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"54283","inspectionDate":"2021-02-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not marked with a consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"48573","inspectionDate":"2019-07-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not safe","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-103.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall ensure that employees, practices and policies are in compliance with the code. (Pf) \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not ensuring compliance","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"Under the Storage rack(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing equipment","subItem":"three compartment sink basins","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Harborage conditions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not eliminated","subProblem":"","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44906","inspectionDate":"2019-01-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In front of","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Under the Condenser","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Under the Storage rack(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"ceiling(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"Missing Ceiling tile(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."}]},{"inspectionid":"41273","inspectionDate":"2018-01-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"37619","inspectionDate":"2017-01-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Food","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\n\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Commercially processed ready to eat potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"6-403.11","violationDescription":"(A) Areas designated for EMPLOYEES to eat, drink, and use tobacco shall be located so that FOOD, EQUIPMENT, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES are protected from contamination.\n(B) Lockers or other suitable facilities shall be located in a designated room or area where contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES can not occur.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Locker(s)/employee storage area(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Contaminates","subProblem":"Food","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean in manner that prevents contamination of other items as specified above."},{"violationCode":"6-403.11","violationDescription":"(A) Areas designated for EMPLOYEES to eat, drink, and use tobacco shall be located so that FOOD, EQUIPMENT, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES are protected from contamination.\n(B) Lockers or other suitable facilities shall be located in a designated room or area where contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES can not occur.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Locker(s)/employee storage area(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Contaminates","subProblem":"Food","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean in manner that prevents contamination of other items as specified above."},{"violationCode":"6-403.11","violationDescription":"(A) Areas designated for EMPLOYEES to eat, drink, and use tobacco shall be located so that FOOD, EQUIPMENT, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES are protected from contamination.\n(B) Lockers or other suitable facilities shall be located in a designated room or area where contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES can not occur.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Locker(s)/employee storage area(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Contaminates","subProblem":"Equipment","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Relocate to a designated area that does not contaminate items or surfaces."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4048"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}